http://www.snowmintcs.com/info/privacy-policy/

Products
Budget
Documentation
Reviews
Budget (Windows)
Reviews
Budget Planner (Windows)
Reviews
Budget Workbook (Windows)
Snowmint Creative Solutions Privacy Statement
At Snowmint Creative Solutions, we recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy is important to us; the information contained herein strives to help you understand just how much personal information is (and is not) collected on our web site and how it is used.
Email addresses
Snowmint Creative Solutions does not purchase or rent bulk email lists. Snowmint Creative Solutions does not sell, trade or rent your email address to others. We sometimes ask for your e-mail address so that we may contact you to inform you of updates, special offers, or other software that we think would be of interest to you. When you participate in a contest, promotion or survey, we may ask for your name, address, e-mail address or other information. We know that the members of our e-mail list are very sensitive to receiving spam, or unsolicited email; hence we are very careful about what we send out and to whom.
You may have yourself removed from our mailing list(s) at any time by simply informing us via email or standard mail. You can find our mailing addresses on our Contact Info web page.
Automatic Information Collection
When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically. On some of the pages of our web site, we do log the IP address of your computer to enable statistical tracking of our web site usage. This does not disclose any personal information about you.
Personal Financial Data
Snowmint Creative Solutions does not collect any personal financial data from our customers. However, Snowmint may request personal financial data from specific customers who report problems with our software. The customer is NOT required to provide this data. Any personal financial data that is sent to us will be held in the strictest confidence and will not be given in any form to any other company or individual. Personal financial data will never be used in any way other than to diagnose and confirm correction of problems in our software.
Software Activity Logging
Our products DO NOT collect any personal information, location information, or computer or phone ID’s. Our software may log user activity used in finding and fixing bugs.
This log is stored on your computing device (computer, phone, or tablet).
Snowmint may request log data from specific customers who report problems with our software. The customer is NOT required to provide this data.
Any activity log data that is sent to us will be held in the strictest confidence and will not be given in any form to any other company or individual.
Log information will never be used in any way other than to diagnose and confirm correction of problems in our software.
Privacy Policies
Snowmint Creative Solutions’ privacy policy is subject to change at any time. We will provide notice 30 days prior to implementing any major changes to our privacy policy. Our web site contains links to other web sites and is not responsible for privacy practices or content of those web sites. We encourage users to learn about the privacy practices of those web sites.
Copryight © 2020 Snowmint Creative Solutions LLCDesign by: TriLion Studios | Code by: Amber Weinberg and Kyle Hammond
Products
Budget
Documentation
Reviews
Budget (Windows)
Budget Planner (Windows)
Budget Workbook (Windows)
